I was walking in the dark I was looking for a sign
I heard a whisper, a distant sound Calling me to
higher ground Felt a hand reach out for me And
suddenly I could see The world was bright and new
I can feel the promise shining down on me I can
hear the call, it's setting me free
It's a beautiful light for the whole world to see
I can feel the promise inside of me
No more shadows, no more doubt. I know what my
life's about. I'm rising up, I'm strong and new.
It's all because I'm following through.
I felt a hand reach out for me. And suddenly, I
could see the world was bright and new.
I can feel the promise
shining down on me. I can hear the call. It's
setting me free.
It's a beautiful light for the whole world to
see. I can feel the promise. Inside of me
Lift your hands up to the sky Let the feeling take
you high
Just let the feeling take you high
I can feel the promise
shining down on me. I can hear the call to set me
free.
It's a beautiful light for the whole world to
see. I can feel the promise. Inside of me He's
coming He's far